tumeapp.com 2012-12-10

# TU Me

## Privacy Policy

**TU ME PRIVACY POLICY**

We know your privacy is important to you. It’s important to us too.

Please read this privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") to understand how we treat your privacy on our Website, when you use the TU Me App and the TU Me service. Before you can use the TU Me service, you will be asked to confirm that you agree to this Privacy Policy.

**Who Are We?**

Telefonica Digital Limited (" **Telefonica Digital** ", "us" or "we") is a company incorporated under the laws of England and Wales with its registered address at 260 Bath Road, Slough, Berkshire SL1 4DX. We control the processing of any information obtained through or in connection with your use of the TU Me services, some of that information may enable you to be identifiable (" **Personal Information** "). Telefonica Digital will be responsible your Personal Information and will decide how it is held and processed. Any Personal Information Telefonica Digital collects from you will be processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Telefonica Digital is part of the Telefonica group of companies (together the " **Telefonica Group Companies** " or " **Telefonica Group** ").

**How do we use information collected from you?**

We want to give you and all of our users the best possible service and an overall positive user experience. That is why we use the Personal Information we collect from you in the following ways:

\- To provide, maintain, tailor and improve the TU Me service;

\- To get in touch to tell you about the TU Me service including, for example, service or security related issues, upcoming changes and improvements, and to let you know about our other products and services you might like;

\- To verify your account access for security purposes;

\- To help you with questions you may have about the TU Me service;

\- To develop new products and services;

\- To protect Telefónica Digital and people that use our services;

\- To anonymise and then to aggregate information about how you and other TU Me users use the service (“ **Aggregate Data** ”) to identify trends and better understand user behaviour. When we say that Aggregate Data is “anonymous” what we mean is that it will not contain information from which you may be personally identified or contacted in any way.

\- To better understand your behaviour in order to personalize and improve the TU Me service for you.

**What information do we collect from you?**

We collect information that you give us and information that we get from your use the TU Me service:

• **Registration Information.** When you sign up for TU ME, we will ask you to give us a screen name and your mobile phone number.

• **Your Activity. **When you use the TU Me service, we collect information about your activity like your communication history and the IP Address you’re using. We use Aggregate Data from Call Detail Records or “CDRs” that allows us to better understand our customers’ usage behavior and trends and to detect potential service problems. In some cases we may look into a specific CDR if a customer requires some support or for public safety reasons or low enforcement reasons. Our servers automatically log your IP Address when you visit our Website and other Website activity including sites linked to/from, ads clicked on, and search terms entered so that we can identify you and gather demographic and behavioral statistics which we use in the form of Aggregate Data. 

• **Device Information.** The TU Me service gathers information from your device, including what device you are using, its operating system and App version, the contact list stored in the device and the localization information of the device. We need this information to give you a better customer experience.

• **Your Contacts.** As part of the TU Me service, if you enable it, the App looks up the phone numbers stored in your address book, sends to the network and stores them remotely to let you know if any of your contacts are already using the TU Me service. The TU Me App service will also let your contacts see that you have signed up to the TU Me Service.

• **Your Content.** A history of the content you enter into the TU Me service (like your contacts, preferences) and the messages you send and receive using the TU Me service form part of your communication history provided by TU Me service and are stored remotely to make it easy for you to retrieve these messages when you need them. We don’t record your calls.

• **Cookies & Other Tracking Technologies.** We may use cookies and other tracking technologies on the Website and in the communications we send to collect information about your surfing activities, likes/dislikes and demographics. You can read more about our use of cookies, web beacons and pixel tags below and in the Website.

• **Correspondence.** We may keep correspondence between you and us to better serve you.

• **Location Data.** We may collect data relating to your location in order to comply with legal obligations, in order to optimize the service provided to you, or in order to personalize the TU Me service. This location data is not collected by use of mobile cell-ID information.

**Who do we share your Personal Information with?**

We don’t share your Personal Information with other organizations or individuals outside of our company, except:

• With carefully selected third parties who will only use the Personal Information in a manner and for purposes specifically agreed by us;

• With the trusted business partners that cooperate with us to provide you the TU Me service or in collecting, storing or processing your information for us. We only provide them with the information they need to perform their specific obligations and we require them to do so based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

• With other companies within the Telefónica group, who will process and use the Personal Information in the same ways and for the same purposes as Telefonica Digital, as set out in this Privacy Policy.

• We sometimes share Aggregate Data with third parties, including trusted advertisers, content providers and business partners or prospective business partners, to give them a better understanding of our business, services and how they are used.

• When we have a good-faith belief that it is reasonably necessary to:

\- meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.

\- enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.

\- detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

\- protect against or prevent harm to the rights, property or safety of Telefónica Digital, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

• With a company that buys us in the event that we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, in order to continue serving you and others.[We may transfer, and you agree to allow us to transfer, your Personal Information to Telefonica Group Companies and other third companies referred above located outside the European Economic Area.]

**How long do we keep your Personal Information?**

We will not keep your Personal Information longer than reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. In any case, if you cancel your account with us, we will no longer process your Personal Information.

**What else do we want you to know?**

**Personal Information of others**

Your contacts are important to you and sharing information with them is the whole point of the TU Me service. That’s why we want to encourage a responsible sharing environment with some basic rules. 

You agree to use the Personal Information you receive from other TU Me users only in connection with the TU Me service. You will not use the Personal Information that is shared with you without the individual user’s express consent. You also agree not to pass along another TU Me user’s Personal Information to any third party without their consent.

You agree that by using the TU Me service other TU Me users who have your mobile number in their contact list or that choose to contact you through the TU Me service will be notified that you have registered for the TU Me service and will have limited access to your certain of your information including your screen name.

**Phone Calls, Messages and Shared Content**

The TU Me service allows phone calls, messages and other content to be sent, received and shared between and among you and your contacts. We can’t guarantee the confidentiality of the information that you communicate to other users, nor do we have any control over the collection and use of your personal information made by our users once you’ve put it out there. Please do not share any Personal Information with any other users that you’d rather keep private.

**Children's Information**

We do not intentionally collect Personal Information from users under thirteen years of age. The TU Me service is not directed or intended for children under thirteen years of age. If you are under thirteen years of age, you should not register and use the TU Me service. If you are the parent or guardian of a user under the age of thirteen, please contact Telefónica Digital at tume@giffgaff.co.uk so that we may delete and remove such user's Personal Information from our system.

**Spam**

Telefónica Digital and its users do not tolerate spam. You agree not to send unsolicited messages to TU Me users and not to add any contact or any other user of the TU Me service to any mailing list or contact list unless you have her express consent.

**Cookies & other technologies on the Website**

We may use cookies on the Website. Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie is sent and stored. We use cookies to improve your experience and personalize the TU Me service. In addition, we may use "clear GIFs" (aka "Web beacons" or "pixel tags") or similar technologies in the Website and/or in our communications so that we can better analyse Website usage information, know whether you have visited a Web page or received a message, or relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information. You may find more information about the cookies we use in the Website.

Please read through our Cookie Policy to find out more about how we use cookies and these other technologies.

**Security**

Telefónica Digital has technical and organisational measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorised access or theft of the Personal Information. We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of the information stored in our platform. However, no method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your Personal Information, unfortunately, we cannot 100% ensure the confidentiality of the communication of any information that you transmit to us or any information that you receive from the TU Me service.

**Changes **

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on our Website. If the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (for example, a text notification via the TU Me service informing you of Privacy Policy changes).

**Contacting Us**

If you wish to access, correct, remove, or prevent processing of any of your personal information, please send your requests, or any questions about this Privacy Policy, to tume@giffgaff.co.uk.

We will do our best to respond promptly and comply with your requests. In some cases we may not be able to process your request, for example, if it is technically impractical, risks the privacy of others, or causes a disproportionate burden on us.

**Effective Date:** 18 June 2012
